new day, right? Another day, how am I going to be if I have the same circumstance in my life,
right? What's a better way for Raj to be or Joe to be the next day? Let me remind myself that I
could be that way tomorrow. I promise you, if you're sincere, just for two, two, three weeks
of doing that, you'll naturally surprise yourself like, wow, I really didn't react to that person.
Wow. I noticed that I was way more calm. I noticed that the person that normally pushes
my buttons. I didn't feel that. And that's one of the crazy things that happens
from our community. They return back into their life. One of the common things people say is,
but I return back into my life and people say, what happened to you? What did you do?
Like, are you on a new drug? Are you taking a new medication? Did you get a face thing?
You got a secret? You're not telling me? You look different, right? Because they are different,
right?